Yeah,
yeah!
Oh!
70 pounds of tactical grace running the
perimeter, securing the space. The instigator
wedges right into the fold while the stoic
anchor comes in from the cold. We've got a riot
squad pacing the floor, waiting for the signal
right outside the door. When the system starts
flashing and the circuits overload, they are
running down the hallway. They are taking up the
road. Bringing the heavy weight, the gravity we
need A living blanket to slow down the speed When
the static is screaming and the processor is
trapped We are safely anchored, perfectly
wrapped Yeah, we are safely anchored,
perfectly wrapped
Down by the jungle room, the siren starts to wail
Arguing with shadows chasing her own tail A
screaming match echoing straight through the
wall With the apex predator refusing to fall
It's an acoustic war in the middle of the night
But it tells the central processor that
everything is right When the system starts
flashing and the circuits overload They are
running down the hallway, they are taking up the
road Bring in the heavyweight, the gravity we
need A living blanket to slow down the speed When
the static is screaming and the processor is
trapped We are safely anchored, perfectly
wrapped Yeah, we are safely anchored,
perfectly wrapped
Deep pressure on the mass. The panic fades to
black. We build a fortress on the floor and we are
coming back. We are coming back!
Bringing the heavy weight, the gravity we need A
living blanket to slow down the speed When the
static is screaming and the processor is
trapped We are safely anchored, perfectly
wrapped
The acoustic water The weighted blanket System
stabilized Hmm.